你好。
Hello.
我，名叫 Phileo
I, am Phileo
我要給你演奏一首歌
I'm going to play a song for you
有關那位敏捷，彩虹色的馬兒
about the fast, rainbow-y horse
但首先，我得邀請你加入我，
But first, I must ask you to join me,
一起到世上最豔麗的小馬聚會
at the world's most alluring pony convention
「Equestria 洛杉磯」
"Equestria LA"
就在今年(2013)的五月
happening this May
也或許，你可能會更想給自己看看
Or perhaps, you'd prefer to feast your eyes
我的搞笑時刻，跟「馬迷俱樂部」一起
upon my silly times with the Brony Clubhouse
這是什麼！？
What is this!?
噓...安靜點，甜心(西班牙文)
Shhhh, silencio mi amor
這首歌並非由吉他開始，
For this song does not begin with a guitar,
而是在那小小的黑膠機上
but on the humble vinyl record
就比如說這邊這台
Much like this one here
來吧，朋友們，
Come with me my friends,
我們的冒險，啟程。
our journey beings.
來，我們學了什麼
Now, what have we learned
很多的控制
Lots of control
很好
Good
大聲尖叫
Screaming and hollering
對，而最重要的是
Yes, and most importantly
熱情
Passion
嘿
Right
那現在你知道歡呼的元素
So now that you know the elements of a good cheer
來，聽一個
let's, hear one
一...二...三...
1... 2... 3...
上！
GO!
一道紅色
Flash of red
鬼神的她飛上天
the spectral wonder takes flight
她很確定，她很堅定，她感覺很爽
and she's ready and she's steady and she's feelin' just right
她有熱情，有動力，有決心要贏
She got the passion, the drive, the tenacity to win
而只要十秒她就能讓你頭昏眼花
and in 10 seconds flat she'll take your head for a spin
天如火燒，彷彿漸漸變成一顆密桃
Sky is burnin' and it's turnin' to a tangerine peach
好像在海南島沙灘的太陽下山
like a sun slowly settin' over Huntington Beach
她的肚子裡有顆火
She's got a fire in her belly
嘿！
Yep!
眼睛裡有火
fire in her eyes
對！
Yes!
超音速的步伐在空中留下火跡
supersonic strut leaves a fire in the skies
越發亮，變成溫暖的金光
Brighten up to a warm and golden glow
讓他充滿你的從腳到頭
let it fill you all up from your head to your toe
讓那太陽閃在你頭
let that sun shine down on ya
大家都叫大聲點
everypony scream louder
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飛過天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我愛她的飛相
I love the way she flies
吼，你要這樣給我喊加油？
Urgh, you're gonna cheer for me like that?
大聲點
Louder
耶
Yay
大聲點
Louder
耶
Yay
大聲點！！！
LOUDER!!!
有片青青草地
We got the green green grass
還有翡翠綠樹
and the emerald trees
還有平原上的兔子、鳥兒，跟蜜蜂
and the meadows with the bunnies and the birds and the bees
而我，真希望能從她的角度看看
and I wish I could see it from her point of view
直接從那，一大片藍天的中間
straight up there in the middle of the big ol' blue
要是可以我一定還會帶你去
and I would if I could and I would take you too
飛過永恆森林，到坎特拉城去
over the Everfree Forest to a Canterlot view
飛到高空中，進入靛色的夜
Flying high up in the sky into the indigo night
星星映照在你的紫色目珠，沒有礙眼物
with the stars in your violet eyes and no care in sight
我沒有任何煩惱
I ain't got no care in sight
當我和你
when I'm with you
我沒有任何煩惱
I ain't got no care in sight
當我和你
when I'm with you
我沒有任何煩惱
I ain't got no care in sight
當我和你
when I'm with you
When I'm with you
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飛過天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我愛她的飛相
I love the way she flies
上吧！
C'mon!
天使飛
Angels fly
衝向邊
Dashing by
閉上眼
Close your eyes
擁抱天
Feel the skies
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飛過天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我愛她的飛相
I love the way she flies
天使飛
Angels fly
衝向邊
Dashing by
閉上眼
Close your eyes
擁抱天
Feel the skies
（別忘了要訂閱！）
還有，看看底下關於 Equestria LA 的資訊
以及馬迷俱樂部
... 對，這是 comic sans*!
* comic sans: 一個被厭惡的字體
相當於標楷體或細明體